const questions = [
  {
    question: 'You or I as a child of God,____ to prosper.',
    optionA: 'is',
    optionB: 'has',
    optionC: 'are',
    optionD: 'am',
    answer: 'am'
  },
  {
    question: 'None of you ____ righteous.',
    optionA: 'is',
    optionB: 'was',
    optionC: 'has ever been',
    optionD: 'are',
    answer: 'are'
  },
  {
    question: 'None of them ____ righteous; said Ade.',
    optionA: 'were',
    optionB: 'is',
    optionC: 'are',
    optionD: 'have ever been',
    answer: 'is'
  },
  {
    question: 'Seventy percent of the problem ____ solved.',
    optionA: 'have been',
    optionB: 'has being',
    optionC: 'has been',
    optionD: 'have being',
    answer: 'has been'
  },
  {
    question: 'John welcomed his guests ____ offered them drinks.',
    optionA: 'and',
    optionB: 'while',
    optionC: 'until',
    optionD: 'as',
    answer: 'and'
  },
  {
    question: 'Two year ago, I _____ English in England.',
    optionA: 'studied',
    optionB: 'was study',
    optionC: 'was reading',
    optionD: 'read',
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: 'You _____ eating when i arrived.',
    optionA: 'was',
    optionB: 'are',
    optionC: 'were',
    optionD: 'have been',
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'He did his best.',
    optionA: "didn't she?",
    optionB: 'does he?',
    optionC: "isn't he",
    optionD: "didn't he?",
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question: 'You or I as a child of God,____ to prosper',
    optionA: 'is',
    optionB: 'has',
    optionC: 'are',
    optionD: 'am',
    answer: 5
  },
  {
    question: 'You or I as a child of God,____ to prosper',
    optionA: 'is',
    optionB: 'has',
    optionC: 'are',
    optionD: 'am',
    answer: 5
  },
  {
    question: 'You or I as a child of God,____ to prosper',
    optionA: 'is',
    optionB: 'has',
    optionC: 'are',
    optionD: 'am',
    answer: 5
  },
]